Hello friends, you are watching Balaav India,
Dheeraj. As we are going to talk
about the Q2 results of IC Lombard General Insurance which came in September 2023
and how were they, then we
will compare it year on year
from September 2022 and for quarter to quarter we
will compare it from June 2023. So
if we look at their sales numbers, their sales this
time have been 5251 crores,
in the previous quarter it was 4694 crores and
in the last quarter it was 6669 crores. So here we will
see that their sales have improved both year on year and
quarter to quarter,
their expenses have increased, this
time their operating profit in this quarter has been 4507 crores,
in the previous quarter it was 400024
crores and in the last quarter it was
crores. If we look at the operating profit, then their operating
profit this time has been 744 crores,
in the previous quarter it was 491 crores, so this
time their profit has been quite good,
in the same quarter last year it was
574 crores  So, their numbers were quite good this time.
If we talk about their margin, which is their
operating profit margin,
what is the percentage, then their margin
this time was 14. In the previous quarter, the
margin was 10 and
in the previous quarter, their margin
was 12. So, their margin has improved this time and hence,
they are earning
more profit. Now, if we talk about their other income,
their income from other business is
only 20 crores. In the previous quarter, it was
29 crores and in the same quarter, it was 36
crores. So, their base income has dropped a bit, year to year, it has
decreased this time from both quarter to quarter. If we
look at the interest, they did
not pay any interest in this quarter, neither in the
previous quarter nor in the same quarter last year,
nothing was paid in the same quarter. There is
no depreciation on theirs either. If
we look at their profit before tax, which is their
profit and how much was it without tax paid, then
in this quarter, they earned 764 crores.
In the previous quarter, it was 520 crores and
in the same quarter it was 610 crores. So,
here also the profit has been made this time.
In this quarter, both year on year and quarter to
quarter, the
profit on tax numbers are good.
Now let's talk about their net profit.
How has the net profit been after paying tax?
This time it has been 577 crores.
In the previous quarter it was 390 crores and
in the same quarter it was 591 crores. So, if we look at it here also, the
net profit has been a little weak year on year, but
quarter to quarter,
because see,
due to this tax,
they had paid less tax here.
See, the profit here was also
less in this quarter than last year, but
tax was paid only on 3, hence
their profit on this is 591 crores,
net profit and here this time the
profit has been more, but they have paid more tax,
due to which their net
profit has come down a little. Overall, if we look at the
numbers, they are good.  Yes, because the margin has also improved, so in this
way, the
September pricing results of ICI Labad General Insurance, if you liked this
video and liked the information, then
definitely like the video and if
you want to see more videos like this, then along with
liking our video, you
can subscribe to the channel,
thank you for watching the entire video, have a nice day.